Gustav Davidson Papers MS038
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Books and Ephemera, 1613 -- 1986; MS038.002; 15.6 Linear Feet
  - Bierstadt, Edward Hale:Dunsany the Dramatist, 1917; MS038.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
    Signature: Gustav Davidson 1917; Little Brown publisher; Fair condition, sticker attached to front cover "Edward Hale Bierstadt letters/correspondence Lord Dunsany letter/signed", wearing to cloth especially at spine; Book plate, signed letter from author glued to front leaf, several pieces of correspondence and clipping along with DJ to A Dreamer's Tales (rehoused in envelope); Originally in bag with Plays of Gods and Men, Jorkens Borrows Another Whiskey, and A Dreamer's Tales
    Biographies
  - Bierstadt, Edward Hale:Dunsany the Dramatist [Ephemera], 1917; MS038.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
    Correspondence and clippings removed from Dunsany the Dramatist
  - Blake, Francis: The American Prometheus, 1964; MS038.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
    Signature: Francis Blake; Five hundred copies of this book have been printed on charcoal white in the month of February MCMXLVI; Very good condition
  - Blake, William: The Book of Urizen, 1958; MS038.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
    Trianon Press; 1/4 bound leather and mabled paper with a slipcase covered in same marbled paper; Review copy of limited edition
    Blake, William
  - Blake, William: The Book of Urizen [Ephemera], 1958; MS038.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
    Envelope that originally housed book
  - Blake, William: Songs of Innocence, 1954; MS038.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
    Trianon Press; 1/4 bound leather and paper in paper covered slipcover, slip leather is flaking; Review copy of limited edition facsimile
  - Bourinot, Arthur S.: More Lines from Deepwood, 1949; MS038.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
    Dedication: Best wishes from Arthur Bourinot; Geo. Shepard Printing Company; Stapled chapbook with minor rusting at staples
  - Browning, Elizabeth Barrett: Sonnets from the Portuguese, 1902; MS038.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
    Putnam Press; Interesting binding with the pages individually taped in place, beautiful color illustrations by Margaret Armstrong, paper is in lovely condition with gilt edges
    Poems; Browning, Elizabeth Barrett
  - Browning, Elizabeth Barrett: Sonnets from the Portuguese, 1910; MS038.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
    Date is approximate; Dedication: To Gustav from [Illegible]; Thomas Mosher Press; Front and back cover detached, red bookmark attached to headband, leather binding; Title page gives pub date as 1810, but that is before it was written. Likely a fifth edition from 1910
  - Bruff, Nancy: My Talon in your Heart, 1946; MS038.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
    Dedication: For Gustav Davidson In fellowship Nancy Bruff June 1969;Water damage; Last page is stuck to flap of DJ, DJ is very torn and fragile, extensive discoloration to cloth; 1st Edition
  - Bunyon, John and John P. Gulliver: The Complete Works of John Bunyon, 1872; MS038.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
    Dedication: darry 1873; One signature of the book only, contains glued in facsimile of the will of John Bunyon, two illustrations and the title page and verso, also in original housing was a separate (likely unrelated) sheet dated 1956 which is in Italian and is possibly part of a Keats book in the collection
  - Bynner, Witter: Journey with Genius Recollections and Reflections Concerning the D.H. Lawrences, 1951; MS038.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
    Dedication: To Gustav Davidson salutations from his friend Witter Bynner [signature of Frieda Lawrence on photo opposite page 84]; John Day Company; DJ is worn and cracked; Originally in bag with Take Away the Darkness and Euripedes II
    Biographies; Lawrence, D.H.
  - Bynner, Witter; Take Away the Darkness, 1947; MS038.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
    Dedication: Finally joining Gustav Davidson I subscribe my satisfaction on July 4th, 1957 in New York Hal Bynner; Knopf Publishing; Minor wear to spine, correspondence removed to envelope; Originally in bag with Journey with Genius and Euripides II
  - Bynner, Witter; Take Away the Darkness [Ephemera], 1947; MS038.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
    Correspondence, clippings and PSA pamphlets removed from Take Away the Darkness
    Poems; Poetry Society of America
  - Callaghan, Gertrude: Witch Girl, 1926; MS038.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
    Dedication: To Gustav with my affection Gertrude; Blue Faun Publication; Text block broken and spine detacting
  - Cane, Melville: January Garden, 1926; MS038.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
    Dedication: For Gustav in friendship, Melville 10/15/58; Harcourt Brace; Price clipped and wear to DJ; In bag with So that It Flower
  - Cane, Melville: So That it Flower, 1966; MS038.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
    Dedication: To my friend Gustav Davidson Melville Crane, 2/20/66; Minor fading to DJ spine; Includes bibliographic card in textblock; 1st edition; In bag with January Garden
  - Careme, Maurice: Images Perdue, 1954; MS038.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
    Dedication:[In French from Maurice Careme to Gustav Davidson 1955]; Front cover detached and top folds are unopened
  - Chubb, Thomas Caldecott: Dante and His World, 1966; MS038.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
    Dedication: For Gustav Davidson who writes about angels this book about a man who saw (?) men Thomas Caldecott Chubb November, 1967; Wear to DJ; 1st edition
    Biographies; Alighieri, Dante
  - Claden, Judith: Rodin the Man and his Art with leaves from his notebook, 1917; MS038.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
    Signature: 1917 [Jessie Sewont-Toausif]; Century Press; Hinges are detaching, wear to corner covers
  - Cox, F.A.: English Madrigals in the Time of Shakespeare, 1917; MS038.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
    Date is estimated; To Gustav Davidson "I think the [?], though dark it be Has aye one rapturious pleasure conceal'd in Life's monotony, For those who seek the treasure; One planet in a stafless night, One blossom on a briar One friend not quite a hypocrite, One Woman not a liar!" Chaunt of the Brazin Heal" Bp. P. Bronstem Christmas Your Birthday 1917; Hinges breakings, wear to spine, cracks in textblock and flaking on edges of pages
  - Cox, Joseph Mason Andrew: Land Dimly Seen, 1975; MS038.002.006.00016 (Box 6)
    Dedication: To Mrs. Mollie Davidson with Best Wishes Joseph Mason Andrew Cox... 20 March 1975...; Discoloration to DJ; First printing January 1975
  - Cox, Joseph Mason Andrew: The Collected Poems of Joseph Mason Andrew Cox, 1970; MS038.002.006.00017 (Box 6)
    Dedication: To Mrs. Gustav Davidson with Best Wishes Joseph Mason Andrew Cox... 8 November 1972...; Very good condition with only slight cracking on DJ; Bibliographic card in textblock
  - Cummins, Virginia Kent: Pierre, 1949; MS038.002.006.00018 (Box 6)
    Dedication: Among the understanding few, I give this book to you -- dear you! For Gustav Davidson with gratitude and admiration from Virginia Kent Cummins Whatever deeds of grace or sinning, whatever dreams or final ends, There's nothing worth the work of winning without the praise and love of friends. V.C. Dec. 1949; Review clipping stuck between pages 44-45 causing discoloration; In bag alone
  - Cuney, William Waring: Storefront Church, 1973; MS038.002.006.00019 (Box 6)
    Dedication: For: Gustav Davidson From: Waring Cuney 4/21/74; Paul Bremen Publishing; Good condition
  - Davidson, Gustav: Half Century of Sonnets, 1924; MS038.002.006.00020 (Box 6)
    Nicholas L. Brown Publisher; Wearing to cover edges, spine is somewhat tight; #9 of 550 copies; Review clipping
    Poems; Davidson, Gustav
  - Davidson, Gustav: Half Century of Sonnets, 1924; MS038.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
    Dedication: To Ben with best wishes Gustav 2/5/24; Nicholas L. Brown Publisher; Front cover detached; #50 of 550 copies
  - Davidson, Gustav: First Editions in American Juvenilia, 1939; MS038.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
    Dedication: For Mollie in affeciation of many things Gustav;Normandie House Publishers; Discoloration to spine; Limited edition
  - Davidson, Gustav: First Editions in American Juvenilia, 1939; MS038.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
    Dedication: To Eva for the sympathetic understanding and devotion Gustav; Normandie House Publishers; Discoloration and breaking to spine; Bill of sale in back cover; Limited edition
  - Davidson, Gustav: In Fealty to Apollo The Poetry Society of America 1910-1950, MS038.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
    Fine Editions Press; DJ is breaking at spine, some wear to bottom edge of cover
    Davidson, Gustav; Poetry Society of America; Fine Editions Press
  - Davidson, Gustav: Thrist of the Antelope, 1945; MS038.002.006.00025 (Box 6)
    Dierkes Press; DJ is torn and fragile; In bag with The Fire's Center, Birthday Poems, James Augustine Joyce, My last Seventy Years, An Interrupted Courtship and Echoes of Childhood; 1st Edition
  - Davidson, Gustav: Twenty Sonnets, 1926; MS038.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
    Dedication: To Miriam Do not fling away ambition though by that sin fell the angels Gustav; Blue Faun Publishers; Spine is worn, deckled paper; DJ not original to publication; 350 copies
  - De Nerval, Gerald and Ludovic Halevy: Sylvie Recollections of Valios, 1887; MS038.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
    George Routledge & Sons Publishers; Some pages detached, wearing to leather spine
  - Decker, Clarence R.: Richard Le Gallienne, 1966; MS038.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
    Apollo Head Press; Good condition; Pamphlet about book in cover; Originally in bag with The Cry of the Little Peoples; Printed for the PSA; 1st edition
    Decker, Clarence; Poetry Society of America
  - Dewitt, S.A.: Shoemaker of the Stars and other poems, 1940; MS038.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
    Dedication: For Gus From S.A. DeWitt; Parnassus Press; Fading of cover, tearing on cover edges
  - Di Lampedusa, Giuseppe and Archibald Colquhoun, trans.: The Leopard, 1961; MS038.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
    Dedication: With many good wishes to Mr. Davidson, from the translator, Archibald Colquhoun January 1963 Allington, Kent U.K.; Collins and Harvill Press; Minor wear to DJ
  - Dickens, Charles: The Adventures of Oliver Twist, 1899; MS038.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
    Date is approximate; Dedication: "Everywhere, everywhere Christmas tonight!" For Mollie and Gustav, Phyllis Christmas, 1947; Thomas Nelson Publisher; Very poor condition, extensive cover deteriation and crease in textblock, ribbon bookmark
    Dickens, Charles
  - Dickens, Charles: The Works of Charles Dickens Household Edition The Old Curiosity Shop Volume II, 1861; MS038.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
    James G. Gregory Publisher; spine starting to crack
  - Dickenson, Emily: The Complete Poems of Emily Dickenson, 1924; MS038.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
    Dedication: For Gustav -- Friend, Poet and Lothario, from one who strives to follow valiently in his steps Leslie Sept. 28 '24; Textblock detached from back cover, leaf in front detatched, discoloration of cover; Clipping and bibliographic card
    Dickenson, Emily
  - Dore, Gustave (illustrator): The Adventures of Baron Munchausen, MS038.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
    Signature: Gustav Davidson; Good condition with fading only on spine. No Date Available
    Dore, Gustave
  - Drake, W. Gordon: In the Cool of the Day, 1956; MS038.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
    Freethought Press Association; Correspondence and accompanying information on play housed in an envelope; Note on page before the forward listing a cast from a 1958 production
    Drama
  - Drake, W. Gordon: In the Cool of the Day [Ephemera], 1956; MS038.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
    Clippings and correspondence from book
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett: A Dreamer's Tales, 1916; MS038.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
    John W. Luce Publisher; DJ no longer intact, found in envelope in Dunsay the Dramatist; Bibliographic card in textblock; In bag with Plays of Gods and Men, Dunsany the Dramatist and Jorkens Borrows Another Whiskey
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett: Jorkens Borrows Another Whiskey, 1954; MS038.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
    Michael Joseph Publisher; Good condition with only minor wear to DJ; Includes bibliographical card and pamphlet on the on poetical works of Lady Wentworth and a clipping; In bag with Plays of Gods and Men, Dunsany the Dramatist, and A Dreamer's Tales
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett: Plays of Gods and Men, 1917; MS038.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
    Dedication: S.L. Samuels 1645- To Gustave Davison who met The ship wherein I crossed, While others were scarce stirring yet, So that I was not lost. [Illegible signature] Feb. 23, 1954; John W. Luce Publisher; Hinges breaking and spine paper coming off; Clipping on Lord Dunsany; In bag with Dunsany the Dramatist, Jorkens Borrows Another Whiskey, and A Dreamer's Tales
  - Eastman, Max: Enjoyment of Living, 1948; MS038.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
    Harper and Brothers Publishing; Minor wear to headbands, bookmark at page 300; In bag with Perennial, Poems of Five Decades, and Lot's Wife; 1st edition
  - Eastman, Max; Lot's Wife, 1942; MS038.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
    Dedication: To my poet friend Gustav Davidson with warmest regards - Max Eastman; Harper and Brothers Publishing; Discoloration and wear to DJ; In bag with Perennial, Poems of Five Decades, and Enjoyment of Living; 1st edition
  - Eastman, Max: Poems of Five Decades, 1954; MS038.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
    Dedication: To my dear friends Gustav and Molly from Max December 4, 1954; Harper and Brothers Publishing; DJ is very fragile and cracked, especially along spine; In bag with Perennial, Enjoyment of Living, and Lot's Wife; 1st edition
  - Edman, Irwin: Ecclesiastes, 1946; MS038.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
    Dedication: To my friend, Gustav Davidson - as a remembrance of Irwin Edman who was a classmate of mine in P.S. 10, B. Manhattan in 1910 -- and later at Columbia School of Journalism, Class of 1917 -- and who was a classmate of yours, at Townsed Harris Hall (which to-day is also a memory) - all, in the dear dead days not yet quite beyond recall. With Affection December XX, 1956 [Illegible Signature]; Odysses Press; Wear to spine
  - Egri, Lajos: Your Key to Successful Writing; A Handbook for the Layman who wants to Write, and for the Writer who wants to Understand the Layman, 1952; MS038.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
    Dedication: For Gustav Davidson In memory of all the [bouti (?) illegible] together Lajos Egri 1952 Oct 31st; Henry Holt Publisher; Apparent water damage; DJ is warped and discolored, text block also slightly warped; Moved clippings and correspondence to envelope; 1st edition
  - Egri, Lajos: Your Key to Successful Writing; A Handbook for the Layman who wants to Write, and for the Writer who wants to Understand the Layman [Ephemera], 1952; MS038.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
    Clippings and correspondence removed from book
  - Eldridge, Paul: Madonna with the Cat, 1942; MS038.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
    Dedication: For Gustav Davidson, cordially, Paul Eldridge; Harbinger House Press; DJ is very torn and discolored, some discoloration of text block; 1st edition
  - Ellis, Edward S.: Uncrowning a King A Story of King Philip's War, 1896; MS038.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
    Dedication: From Jay Lewis; New Amsterdam Book Company; Severe discoloration to cover, top and bottom of spine breaking away, textblock detached from back cover, discoloration to edges of paper; Business card for Jay Lewis, The Ledger- Dispatch Norfolk, VA inside
  - Ellis, Richard: Book Illustration A Survey of its History and Development, 1952; MS038.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
    Bookplate for Gustav and Mollie Davidson; Kingsport Press; Very good condition; In bag labeled Richard Ellis Printer along with Tom Jones and Five Hundred Years of Printing from Type; also designed by Richard Ellis
  - Ellis, Richard: Five Hundred Years of Printing from Type, 1940; MS038.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
    Dedication: To Gustav Davison - Craftsman and Poet and Publisher for my old friend and fellow lover of books and typography from the author, printer Richard Ellis At a meeting, after many years New York 23 June 4 + 5; Haddon Craftsmen; Wear and discoloration to cover, particularly at spine; In bag labeled Richard Ellis Printer along with Tom Jones and Book Illustrations; also designed by Richard Ellis; Correspondence removed to envelope
  - Ellis, Richard: Five Hundred Years of Printing from Type [Ephemera], 1940; MS038.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
    Correspondence removed from book
  - Ellis, Richard and Earl Schench, ed.: Bookmaking and Kindred Amenities, 1942; MS038.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
    Dedication: for Gustav - poet, writer and friend with affection ever from the printer editor Richard 16th October 4+7; Rutgers University Press; Fading, tearing, and dirt on DJ, front cover is in early stage of detaching; Removed extensive correspondence in front cover, several Christmas cards and two letters on containing a poem "Song of the Spirit" by GD, also three photos (which I folded in acid-free paper)
  - Ellis, Richard and Earl Schench, ed.: Bookmaking and Kindred Amenities [Ephemera], 1942; MS038.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
    Correspondence and ephemera removed from book
  - Fay, Alice: Our America A Symphony of the New World, 1929; MS038.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
    G.P. Putnam Sons Publisher; DJ is deteriorating and torn; Clipping placed in envelope, several clippings stapled into front leaves of book
    Poems; Fay, Alice
  - Fay, Alice: Our America A Symphony of the New World [Ephemera], 1929; MS038.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
    Materials removed from Our America: A Symphony of the New World
  - Fay, Alice: Our America A Symphony of the New World, 1929; MS038.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
    G.P. Putnam Sons Publishers; Revisions glued into textblock and list of revisions on page 104; Paperclip removed from pages 35-40, DJ faded and torn
  - Fay, Alice: Our America A Symphony of the New World, 1929; MS038.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
    G.P. Putnam Sons Publishing; Extensive fading to DJ
  - Fay, Alice:The Realm of Fancy, 1912; MS038.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
    Broadway Publishing Company; DJ is thin, waxy paper that is very torn and yellowed, minor foxing to inside cover
  - Fay, Alice: The Soul's Quest, 1936; MS038.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
    G.P. Putnam Sons Publishing; pp. 92-94 have notes in pen; Minor tearing to DJ, DJ spine fading
  - Fay, Alice: The Soul's Quest, 1936; MS038.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
    G.P. Putnam Sons Publishing; pp. 92-95 have notes in pen and glued in note; Minor tearing to DJ, DJ spine fading, price clipped
  - Ferguson, George Wells: Signs and Symbols in Christian Art with Illus. from painting in the Renaissance, 1954; MS038.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
    Dedication: A gift for your library! This interesting work, I pursued and saw through the press for my friend Rush Kress; for my very dear friend and bookish counselor of over forty years, Gustav Davidson, whose literary and poetic genius is now absorbed in a Dictionary of Angels, I now inscribe this book thus: To my Angelic friend, whith the homage and Love of the Printer Devil, Richard Ellis In my Library 1325 Pine Shui Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Sunday the 9th of July 1967 In your presence and Mollie's and my Kathryn's after a happy and memorable visit; Oxford University Press; Very good condition with only minor fading to cover; Correspondence and photos from Richard Ellis (put in sleeve and labeled) photo includes picture of Ellis holding a copy of The four gospels and acts of the apostles; Designed by Richard Ellis for the Samuel H. Kress Foundation
    Ellis, Richard
  - Ferguson, George Wells: Signs and Symbols in Christian Art with Illus. from painting in the Renaissance [Ephemera], 1954; MS038.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
    Ephemera removed from book including correspondence and photographs
  - Field, Roswell M.: The Passing of Mother's Portrait, 1948; MS038.002.008.00010 (Box 8)
    Trovillion Private Press; Discoloration of spine; In bag with sticker "signed #224" although book does not appeared to be signed
  - Fielding, Henry: The History of Tom Jones A Foundling Volume 1, 1924; MS038.002.008.00011 (Box 8)
    Signature: Gustav Davidson 1926; Knopf Publishing; Wear at headbands, some pages not opened; blue sticker with # on front cover; In bag labeled Richard Ellis Printer along with Book Illustrations and Five Hundred Years of Printing from Type; Designed by Richard Ellis; 1491 of 3000 copies
  - Finger, Charles J.: The Affair at the Inn as seen by Philo the Innkeeper and the Taxgatherer of Rome, 1937; MS038.002.008.00012 (Box 8)
    Dedication: for Gustav - a dear friend & fellow booklover - with all good wishes of the printer Richard; Haddon Craftsmen Press; Some evidence of acid mitgration on pages, discoloration to cover; Designed by Richard Ellis; 1000 copies
  - Fitzgerald, Geoffrey: Rockets in the Afternoon, 1946; MS038.002.008.00013 (Box 8)
    Dedication: for Gustav whose patient help and kindly advice is by and large responsible for launching my new and brighter day -- Geoffrey Fitzgerald Oct. 11, 1946; Fine Editions Press; Good condition
  - Flaubert, Gustave and Rene Francis ed.: The First Temptation of Saint Anthony, 1924; MS038.002.008.00014 (Box 8)
    John Lane Publishing; Text block cracking, worn spine edges, blue sticker on cover
  - Folgore da San Gimignano and Thomas Caldecott Chubb, Trans.: The Months of the Year, 1960; MS038.002.008.00015 (Box 8)
    Dedication: For Gustav Davison poet and good friend of poetry Thomas Caldecott Chubb January 15, 1961; Wake-Brook House; From the Decameron by Boccaccio; Good condition
  - Fountain, Helen: A Cage of Birds, 1970; MS038.002.008.00016 (Box 8)
    Dedication: To Mollie Davidson With Best Wishes, Helen Fountain Aug. 1971; Golden Quill Press; Acid migration on inside cover of DJ; Correspondence and promotional card for book were inside front cover, removed to envelope
  - Fountain, Helen: A Cage of Birds [Ephemera], 1970; MS038.002.008.00017 (Box 8)
    Correspondence and promotional material removed from book
  - Frost, Lesley: Really Not Really, 1962; MS038.002.008.00018 (Box 8)
    Signature: Lesley Frost September 1962; Channel Press; Wear to DJ, Price clipped; In bag by itself
  - Frost, Robert: A Masque of Mercy, 1947; MS038.002.008.00019 (Box 8)
    Henry Holt Publishing; DJ is very torn and discolored, especially along spine; Review by Davidson glued inside front cover; In bag with In the Clearing and The Pastorial Art of Robert Frost; 1st Printing
    Frost, Robert
  - Frost, Robert: In the Clearing, 1962; MS038.002.008.00020 (Box 8)
    Holt, Rinehart, and Winston Publishing; Very minor tearing to DJ; In bag with A Masque of Mercy and The Pastorial Art of Robert Frost; 1st edition
    Poems; Frost, Robert
  - Frost, Robert and Louis Untermeyer: The Letters of Robert Frost to Louis Untermeyer, 1963; MS038.002.008.00021 (Box 8)
    Holt, Rinehard,and Winston; Some dog-eared pages; Two index cards in textblock; In bag separately; 1st edition
  - Ginsberg, Louis: Morning in Spring and Other Poems, 1970; MS038.002.008.00022 (Box 8)
    Signature: Louis Ginsberg Allen Ginsberg [and drawing of flower]; William Morrow Publishing; Acid migration on inside of back cover and front cover; In bag with correspondence and additional correspondence removed from front cover to envelope
    Poems; Ginsberg, Louis; Ginsberg, Allen
  - Ginsberg, Louis: Morning in Spring and Other Poems [Ephemera], 1970; MS038.002.008.00023 (Box 8)
    Correspondence removed from front cover of book
    Ginsberg, Louis
  - Gogarty, Oliver St. John: Intimations, 1950; MS038.002.008.00024 (Box 8)
    Signature: Oliver St. John Gogarty; Abelard Press; DJ placed in envelope; Poem taped to back page; In bag with It Isn't This Time of Year at All and collected Poems; 1st edition
    Gogarty, Oliver St. John
  - Gogarty, Oliver St. John: Intimation [Ephemera], 1950; MS038.002.008.00025 (Box 8)
    Dust jacket for book
  - Gogarty, Oliver St. John: It Isn't This Time of Year at All, 1954; MS038.002.008.00026 (Box 8)